markets extend decline for a third
straight session Nifty fails to hold on
to the opening gains index off drops
below 18,200 Mark broader markets remain
Under Pressure defensive stocks among
the top losers but PSU Banks defy
weakness once
[Music]
again big day as far as earnings is
concerned the lights of Js W steel TVs
motor biocor Asian paints some of the
important
numbers margin Miss sends hav stumbling
in trade management hints at PR Heights
in the next couple of months expects
margin to stabilize going forward
meanwhile jubilan food continues to feel
the heat in trade as the company sees
inflationary pressure playing out for
the next few next few quarters
it's an 18 now exclusive you heard it
first on the times Network it's
confirmed pnz board will be considering
2,000 crores of fundraising on November
2nd this is after terminating the deal
with carile
[Music]
International lenders are batting bigon
open Credit
enablement Network which is also known
as oen sour of sales the banks like SBI
and access bank kot Mahindra bank and
Bajaj Finance are gearing up to join ocm
soon the platform May provide scope for
reducing the lending rates even further
and that's a need now exclusive
[Music]